{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473897874","data":{"timestamp":" 947473897874"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kitu-kuwa-yule"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473906769","data":{"timestamp":" 947473906769"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_umwa_amua-choo-umwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" umwa"," userResponse":" umwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473918514","data":{"timestamp":" 947473918514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_huwa-waje-tele"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473935160","data":{"timestamp":" 947473935160"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ziwa_tani-ziwa-kuna"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ziwa"," userResponse":" ziwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473943836","data":{"timestamp":" 947473943835"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mpwa_zote-kifo-mpwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mpwa"," userResponse":" mpwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473952852","data":{"timestamp":" 947473952852"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_jivu-kuwa-wale"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473961553","data":{"timestamp":" 947473961553"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_kuwa-giza-humu"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473970774","data":{"timestamp":" 947473970774"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dawa_debe-yule-dawa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dawa"," userResponse":" dawa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473979084","data":{"timestamp":" 947473979084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_huwa_huwa-lisa-miye"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" huwa"," userResponse":" huwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473990512","data":{"timestamp":" 947473990512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_pesa-kwao-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuwa"," userResponse":" kuwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.wa.show.31","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947473996299","data":{"timestamp":" 947473996297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 7f0868ba-9242-4fcd-8a29-137c31657736"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_end.wrd.wa.show.31"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kuwa_pesa-kwao-kuwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474020749","data":{"timestamp":" 947474020749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mpwa_mpwa_ikiwa_mbawa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474027387","data":{"timestamp":" 947474027387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" ziwa_ziwa_nilikuwa_itakuwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474034006","data":{"timestamp":" 947474034005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lililokuwa_zilikuwa_alishindwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474041469","data":{"timestamp":" 947474041468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lililokuwa_zilikuwa_alishindwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474052172","data":{"timestamp":" 947474052172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lililokuwa_zilikuwa_alishindwa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474058832","data":{"timestamp":" 947474058832"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" palikuwa_palikuwa_njiwa_imefungwa"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474065451","data":{"timestamp":" 947474065450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" yalikuwa_yalikuwa_maziwa_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474072102","data":{"timestamp":" 947474072101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hewa_hewa_ingawa_nilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474078761","data":{"timestamp":" 947474078760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" alijawa_huwa_alijawa_alipewa"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474085401","data":{"timestamp":" 947474085400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mpendwa_mkubwa_palikuwa_mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474092870","data":{"timestamp":" 947474092870"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" mpendwa_mkubwa_palikuwa_mpendwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474099495","data":{"timestamp":" 947474099495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" lilikuwa_akiwa_akawa_lilikuwa"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474106111","data":{"timestamp":" 947474106111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474113589","data":{"timestamp":" 947474113589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474124292","data":{"timestamp":" 947474124292"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.wa.show.15","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947474136346","data":{"timestamp":" 947474136346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000110_061112"," gameId":" 8ff6928e-7e38-4298-bd90-65f202f47472"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.wa.show.15"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" makubwa_alikunywa_makubwa_machungwa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}